bannerflow.com 2011-04-10

# Bannerflow - Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

_October 15, 2008_

This privacy policy explains how Bannerflow, LLC (“Bannerflow”) handles personal information, creative assets and non-personal information when you use Bannerflow products and services. This website, www.bannerflow.com (the “Site”), is owned and operated by Bannerflow.

**_Personal Information and How It Is Used_**

In order to use the Site or Bannerflow services, it is may be necessary to provide personal information such as your name, company name, email address, billing address, and credit card information.

Your personal information is processed and maintained by Bannerflow for a number of purposes, including the following: identification and authentication, access to the Bannerflow services, services improvement, contact and research and payment of Bannerflow services fees.

Bannerflow uses third-party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run Bannerflow. Bannerflow may share your personal information, creative assets or non-personal information with such third-party vendors that perform services on Bannerflow's behalf, for example, companies that provide support services to us (such as credit card processing services, data storage services, and web hosting services) or that help us market Bannerflow products and services (such as third-party e-mail marketing companies). These third parties are required by contract to use the personal information or creative assets Bannerflow shares with them only to perform services on Bannerflow's behalf and to treat your personal information and creative assets as confidential. 

**_Sharing of Personal Data and Security_**

Bannerflow is committed to keeping your personal information and creative assets private. Except as set forth in privacy policy or as required by law, Bannerflow will not share your personal information and creative assets with any company or individual. Bannerflow processes all Bannerflow service orders on a secure server that encrypts all financial information through Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) data encryption. Although total security does not exist on the Internet, Bannerflow shall make commercially reasonable efforts to safeguard the personal information and creative data that you submit to Bannerflow or the Site.

If you submit your banner advertisements to Bannerflow “Showcase,” such banner advertisements shall be publicly available to those visitors to the Site 

**_Sharing and Transfer of Information_**

It may be necessary for Bannershare to share your personal information or creative assets with outside parties as necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Bannerflows’ Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law. 

Bannerflow may share your information in circumstances where you have requested additional services, or provided permission.

Your personal information and creative assets may be transferred or assigned if Bannerflow is acquired or merged with another company. You will be notified by email to your most recent address in our files or by a notice on the Site before any of your personal information or creative assets are transferred or becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

**_Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information_**

In addition to the personal information or creative assets you supply, Bannerflow may collect non-personal information to evaluate how visitors, guests, and customers use the Site and the Bannerflow services. Bannerflow collects non-personal data to make the Site and Bannerflow services work better for you in the following ways: to improve the design of the Site or the Bannerflow services, to provide personalization of the Site and to evaluate the performance of our marketing programs. The technologies Bannerflow uses to gather this non-personal information may include “IP” addresses, “cookies”, “clear gifs”, browser detection, and “web logs”. 

Cookies are used for authenticating, session tracking and maintaining specific information about users, such as Site preferences. A cookie is a small amount of data stored on your hard drive. You may modify your browser preferences to accept all cookies, be notified when a cookie is set, or reject all cookies. Bannerflow services may require cookies in order to function properly.

“IP” addresses are unique identifying numbers for computers on the Internet and help Bannerflow better understand the geographic distribution of our members and manage the performance of this Site. 

Bannerflow also may use a technology called "clear gifs". Clear gifs are tiny graphics with unique identifiers that are used to track emails and online movements, helping Bannerflow understand what marketing campaigns and content are effective.

Bannerflow may detect the type of web browser you are using to optimize the performance of the Site and to understand the mix of browsers used by Bannerflow visitors, guests, and customers. To learn about how people use the Site, Bannerflow examines “web logs”, which show the paths people take through the Site and how long they spend in certain areas.

**_Policy Revisions_**

Bannerflow reserves the right to periodically change this privacy policy. In the event that this privacy policy materially changes, Bannerflow will notify you via email to the address in our files or by posting a notice of such update to the Bannerflow website. You are responsible for reviewing this Site periodically for any changes to this privacy policy. Any access or use of the Site by you after notice of changes to this privacy policy shall constitute your agreement to such revisions or additions. 

**_Right to Review, Update or Change Data_**

You can access and maintain your personal information via the "My Account" area on the Site. To protect your privacy and security, Bannerflow requires a Member ID and password to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**_Privacy Preferences and Opting-Out_**

When you sign up as a user of the Bannerflow services you may begin receiving marketing communications such as e-mail newsletters, product and service updates or promotions. If you do not want to receive these communications, you must “opt-out” by unchecking the “Add me to the mailing list” box on the registration page, or should you choose to opt-out after registering, you can use any of the following three methods: select the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of the email and follow the opt-out instructions; go to My Account area of the Site, select “Manage Account”, then select “Change Communication Preferences” and de-select the appropriate box; or send an email to unsubscribe@bannerflow.com from the email account that receives the unwanted messages.

**_Contact Us_**

If you have any questions about the Bannerflow Privacy Policy, please contact us at support@bannerflow.com.
